

## **MAHAMADI** CONGO

### SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

### CONTACT

- +49 177 7420 577
- Priesestr 81, 12053 Berlin
- linkedin.com/in/mahamadi-congo

#### **PROFILE**

Highly skilled Software Developer with experience in both front-end and back-end development. Proficient in JavaScript, ReactJS, Node.js, and various frameworks. Strong problem-solving abilities and a track record of delivering quality software solutions in collaboration with development teams and stakeholders.

# EDUCATION & TRAINING

## Full-Stack Developer Training DCI DIGITAL CAREER INSTITUTE

- 1-year intensive training in Web Development with real-life projects.
- Covered Node.js, React, JavaScript, MongoDB, Git.

## Online Course WARDIERE UNIVERSITY

- Certificate of Achievement, 2018 -2020
- Studied JavaScript, Python, React,Node.js & MongoDB

### <u>SKILLS</u>

- Front End: JavaScript,
   TypeScript, HTML/CSS,
   ReactJS,Next.js, Bootstrap,
   Tailwind, Storybook, styled-components
- Back End: Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB
- Tools & Systems: VSCode,
   Docker, Git, GitHub, GitLab,
   Jira, Figma

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **TA Europe**

Software Developer

Oct 2021 - Jan 2024

- Design and develop software solutions for front-end applications in collaboration with the development team and stakeholders.
- Conduct feasibility tests for software prototypes and modify code to fix errors.

#### Zalando

Jun 2021 - Sep 2021

Intern Software Developer

• Developed and implemented software solutions for Zalando retail based on provided designs.

#### **Staiy**

Feb 2021 - Jun 2021

Intern Software Developer

- Developed and implemented software solutions based on Figma designs.
- Tested and refined software prior to rollout and released ad hoc product patches.

#### LANGUAGE

- France (First language)
- English (Advanced)
- German (Intermediate)

#### REFERENCE

#### Sebastian Frohwann

Phone: +49 173 463 53 86

COO / Partner

CTO (Chief Technology Officer)

Phone: +4917670228902

Patrick Da Silva